The kettle and the idol
The third is "various ah?
Various ah?
You have to listen to it to understand it at all.
I was told to narrow it down to three, so I thought it would be difficult, so I just crammed them all in here.
My name is Miya, so it's like "Aga-ai. Miya.
I call her Miya with love in my heart.
I think that love is a part of me that I cherish on a daily basis.
The first "A" is "A" for love.
It's the first "A." The first "A.
The first "A".
Love.
There are many more "A "s, aren't there?
Yes, there are. I also try to greet people with greetings, so after the greetings........
I see. I see...Mya's, greetings, and other important ahs will continue to appear in the future, won't they?
That's right. And then there is the "ah" of mockery.
Mocking ah.
Mocking. But that's okay. The person who says it to himself is a mocking person.
I think it's good. You're a mocking person.
Yes, it is. But I wasn't so aware of it in the past.
I love my fans, so I think about what I can do to make them happy.
I was thinking about how I could make my fans happy and what would make me happy if I were them, and as a result of that I became more and more bruised.
The word "mocking" might sound a bit negative, but it is not.
I was thinking about my fans, and that's how I ended up like this.
That's all there is to it.
It was like I was blaming the fans.
That's right.
That's a bit of a mockery, isn't it?
Yes, it is. But I like it, so it's good.
Is there such a thing as a mocking pose?
Mocking poses?
Yes, there is.
Yes, I do.
Oh?
There are two.
May I? Could you please face the volume camera?
Here's the first one.
That's a little bit of a trick.
Oh, I see.
The second one, please.
And the second one is more of a flow, or there's some pretending before we get to the pose.
Yes, yes, yes. What kind of poses?
Otsu-pippi, perfect meya.
Oh, I see.
This is not because of Mr. Popper.
If I thought Mr. Popper would be happy with this pose, it would be this pose.
Two.
Yes, two.
I got them from such a mocking pose.
A mocking in the benefit world.
Yes, that's right. A pompous person in the world of perks.
Is there anything that you do that is so mocking that even you, Popper, would say it is mocking?
What I've been doing lately is looking people in the eye and talking to them.
I never turn my eyes away.
And when posing, people often look forward like this and make a peace.
When they take an "Axe shot" or something like that.
At that time, we usually don't have a chance to talk face to face, so we ask them to take a picture of us looking at each other.
I have been taking pictures of us looking at each other.
I've been taking pictures of people who turn their eyes away, or their ears turn red, and their faces turn red, and their faces turn red, and their eyes turn away.
I know, right?
There are quite a few people like that, and it makes me very happy to see them, and
It makes me happy, doesn't it?
It makes me happy to know that there are people who blush when they see me.
It is also an opportunity for me to want to play with them.
It definitely makes me happy. That moment.
Thank you for watching.
This program was presented by Miyakkun, Kokona, Keisuke, Ukyou, and Tatsu.
Miya would love to meet you.
Thank you very much for your contribution!